Guide to the Hisham Khatib Collection of photographic prints AD.MC.030
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
- Postcards, 731 (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
  - A hand-colored postcard of the Damascus Gate in Jerusalem (Porte de Damas - no.149)., Circa 1900-1950; ref533; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Hand-colored Photographs/Hand-tinting; Palestine; Damascus Gate, Jerusalem; Crowds; Regional/National Dress; Buildings; Architecture; French Writing; English Writing; Italian Writing; Men; Women; Head Covers/Veils; Streets/Roads; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts
  - A postcard of the cemetery of Mount Zion., Circa 1900-1950; ref534; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Mount Zion/Jabal Sahyoun, Jerusalem; Palestine; Cemeteries; Buildings; Architecture; English Writing; French Writing; Mosques; Religious Sites; Tombs/Mausoleums; Buildings
  - A postcard of an altar in Cavalry at the Church of the Holy Sepulchre., Circa 1900-1950; ref535; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Churches; Church of the Holy Sepulchre; Jerusalem; Palestine; Religious Sites; Religious Imagery; Chandeliers; French Writing; English Writing; Buildings
  - A postcard of the Garden of Gethsemane in Jerusalem (Jordin de Gethsemane)., 1936; ref536; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Palestine; Gethsemane, Jerusalem; Buildings; Architecture; Gardens; Religious Sites; Landscapes; English Writing; Italian Writing
  - A postcard of an illustration of the Temple of Solomon., Circa 1900-1950; ref537; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Buildings; Architecture; Religious Sites; Temples; Jerusalem; Palestine; English Writing; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts
  - A postcard of an illustration of a stadium (or racecourse)., Circa 1900-1950; ref538; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Architecture; Buildings; Stadiums; English Writing; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts
  - A postcard of an illustration of the eastern rock-hewn tomb., 28 December 1907; ref539; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Tombs/Mausoleums; English Writing; Postal Stamps; Religious Sites
  - A hand-colored postcard of the River Jordan., 1935; ref540; Missionary Film Committee, 59 New Oxford Street, WC1, London (England) (active 1930s); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Jordan River; Rivers; Palestine; English Writing; Landscapes; Postal Stamps; Postal Stamps; Photographic Prints; Hand-colored Photographs/Hand-tinting
  - A postcard of the Tree of the Agony in the Garden of Gethsemane., Circa 1900-1950; ref541; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Gethsemane, Jerusalem; Gardens; Religious Sites; English Writing; Palestine; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Landscapes
  - A postcard of the second station in Jerusalem (no. 1055)., Circa 1900-1950; ref542; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Jerusalem; Palestine; Buildings; Architecture; Men; Regional/National Dress; Photographic Prints; English Writing; German Writing; French Writing; Streets/Roads; Street Lamps; Individual Portraits
  - A hand-colored postcard of the Church of the Redeemer (German Church), Jerusalem., Circa 1900-1950; ref543; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Hand-colored Photographs/Hand-tinting; Jerusalem; Palestine; Buildings; Architecture; Churches; Religious Sites; English Writing; French Writing; German Writing; Men; Regional/National Dress; French Writing
  - A postcard of the interior of the Church of the Nativity in Bethlehem (no. 628)., Circa 1900-1950; ref544; The Oriental and Commercial Bureau, Port Said, Egypt; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Bethlehem; West Bank; Palestine; Buildings; Architecture; Church of the Nativity; Churches; Religious Sites; English Writing; French Writing; German Writing
  - A hand-colored postcard of the Chapel of the Ascension., Circa 1900-1950; ref545; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Hand-colored Photographs/Hand-tinting; Photographic Prints; Religious Sites; Monuments/Memorials; Mount of Olives/Jabal al-Zaytun, Jerusalem; Buildings; Architecture; Palestine; French Writing; English Writing; German Writing; Chapel of the Ascension; Churches; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts
  - A postcard of the Grotto of the Nativity (no. 630)., Circa 1900-1950; ref546; The Oriental and Commercial Bureau, Port Said, Egypt; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Bethlehem; West Bank; Palestine; Churches; Religious Sites; Photographic Prints; Religious Imagery; Church of the Nativity; English Writing; French Writing; German Writing
  - A postcard of a man looking towards Absalom's Pillar and tombs of St. James and Zacharias. (no. 197)., Circa 1900-1950; ref547; Pinhassovitz & Schwartz, Tel-Aviv, Palestine; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Landscapes; Men; Buildings; Architecture; Tombs/Mausoleums; Monuments/Memorials; English Writing; French Writing; Tomb of Absalom; Tomb of Zechariah; Tomb of Benei Hezir; Kidron Valley; Cemeteries; Church of Mary Magdalene, Jerusalem; Churches; Religious Sites; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Palestine
  - A postcard of the Church of Mary Magdalene and Garden of Gethsemane., Circa 1900-1950; ref548; Benor-Kalter, J., 1897-1969; S (Samuel). Adler, Haifa, Palestine PO Box 960, Hadar Hacarmel (Active 1933-1934); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Photographic Prints; Palestine; Gethsemane, Jerusalem; Gardens; Buildings; Architecture; Religious Sites; Churches; Mount of Olives/Jabal al-Zaytun, Jerusalem; English Writing; Hebrew Writing; Church of Mary Magdalene, Jerusalem
  - A postcard of a the Golden Gate in Jerusalem (116)., Circa 1900-1950; ref549; Fr. Vester and Co. (Jerusalem, Palestine); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Photographic Prints; Jerusalem; Palestine; Golden Gate, Jerusalem; Buildings; Architecture; Temple Mount/al-Ḥaram al-Šarīf; English Writing; French Writing; German Writing; Religious Sites; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts
  - A postcard of Temple Mount/al-Ḥaram al-Šarīf and general view of Jerusalem from the Mount of Olives//Jabal al-Zaytun., Circa 1900-1950; ref550; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Landscapes; Buildings; Architecture; Jerusalem; Palestine; Dome of the Rock/Qubbat al-Sakhrah; English Writing; Photographic Prints; Temple Mount/al-Ḥaram al-Šarīf; Mount of Olives/Jabal al-Zaytun, Jerusalem
  - A hand-colored postcard of the Mosque of Kait Bey (Complex of Sultan al-Ashraf Qaytbay) in Cairo. (no. 63)., Circa 1900-1950; ref551; Lehnert & Landrock; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Hand-colored Photographs/Hand-tinting; Mosque and Tomb of Sultan al-Ashraf Qaitbay; Mosques; Religious Sites; Buildings; Architecture; Egypt; Animals; Shops; Men; English Writing
  - A hand-colored postcard of a group of men and camels leaving the Citadel in Cairo (no.56)., Circa 1900-1950; ref552; Lehnert & Landrock; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Hand-colored Photographs/Hand-tinting; Photographic Prints; Animals; Camels; Buildings; Architecture; Citadel, Cairo, Egypt; Religious Sites; Mosques; English Writing; Men
  - A hand-colored postcard of the Blue Mosque (no.60)., Circa 1900-1950; ref553; Lehnert & Landrock; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Hand-colored Photographs/Hand-tinting; Photographic Prints; English Writing; Egypt; Men; Women; Turbans; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Buildings; Architecture; Mosques; Religious Sites; Streets/Roads
  - A hand-colored postcard of a boat in the Suez Canal in Kantara (El Qantara)., Circa 1899-1908; ref554; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Hand-colored Photographs/Hand-tinting; Photographic Prints; Egypt; Canals; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Animals; English Writing; Landscapes
  - A hand-colored postcard of camels passing the Suez Canal in Kantara (El Qantara)., Circa 1899-1908; ref555; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Hand-colored Photographs/Hand-tinting; Photographic Prints; English Writing; Animals; Camels; Men; Regional/National Dress; Canals; Buildings; Egypt; Boats/Ships; Transportation
  - A postcard of a ship in the quay of Port Said. (Port Said - Le Quai)., Circa 1899-1908; ref556; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Photographic Prints; Port Said, Egypt; Seas; Mediterranean Sea; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Buildings; Docks/Piers/Jetties; French Writing; English Writing; Landscapes
  - A postcard of Port Said Lighthouse (Port Said - Le Phare)., Circa 1899-1908; ref557; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Photographic Prints; Men; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Port Said, Egypt; Seas; Mediterranean Sea; Lighthouses; Buildings; Architecture; French Writing; English Writing
  - A postcard of the statue of Ferdinand de Lesseps at Port Said (Port Said - Ferdinand de Lesseps)., Circa 1899-1908; ref558; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Port Said, Egypt; French Writing; English Writing; Buildings; Statues/Sculptures; Monuments/Memorials; Boats/Ships; Seas; Transportation; Mediterranean Sea
  - A postcard of a boat in the quay at Port Said (Port Said - Le Quai)., Circa 1899-1908; ref559; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; French Writing; English Writing; Photographic Prints; Buildings; Boats/Ships; Hotels; Transportation; Seas; Mediterranean Sea; Port Said, Egypt; Landscapes
  - A postcard of a statue-fountain of Queen Victoria at Port Said., Circa 1899-1908; ref560; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Photographic Prints; Statues/Sculptures; Fountains; Monuments/Memorials; Royalty; Port Said, Egypt; Men; Drinks/Beverages; French Writing; English Writing; Group Portraits
  - A postcard of a shop-lined street in Port Said (Port Said - Rue de Commerce)., Circa 1899-1908; ref561; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Photographic Prints; Port Said, Egypt; Men; Women; French Writing; English Writing; Shops; Buildings; Streets/Roads; Street Lamps
  - A postcard of a ship in the Suez Canal (Le Canal de Suez)., Circa 1899-1908; ref562; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Photographic Prints; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Seas; Landscapes; French Writing; Egypt; English Writing
  - A postcard of ships at Port Said (Port Said - Le Port), Circa 1899-1908; ref563; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Photographic Prints; Seas; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Mediterranean Sea; Buildings; Port Said, Egypt; French Writing; English Writing
  - A postcard of the quay at Port Said, with the lighthouse in the background. (Port Said - Le Quai)., Circa 1899-1908; ref564; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Photographic Prints; Port Said, Egypt; French Writing; English Writing; Buildings; Lighthouses; Landscapes
  - A postcard of the quay and the Suez Canal company office at Port Said. (Le Quai et le Bureau de la Compagnie)., Circa 1899-1908; ref565; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Buildings; Port Said, Egypt; Architecture; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Seas; Mediterranean Sea; French Writing; English Writing; Landscapes
  - A postcard of the Suez Canal at Port Said (Port Said - Le Canal)., Circa 1899-1908; ref566; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Port Said, Egypt; Seas; Mediterranean Sea; Buildings; French Writing; English Writing; Landscapes
  - A postcard of four women, one holding a tambourine (Port Said - Musique Arabe)., Circa 1899-1908; ref567; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Group Portraits; Women; Regional/National Dress; Port Said, Egypt; Musical Instruments; Musicians; Head Covers/Veils; Tambourines; French Writing; English Writing
  - A postcard of the Ismaïlia Canal (Port Said - Ismaliah le Canal)., Circa 1899-1908; ref568; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Port Said, Egypt; Canals; French Writing; English Writing; Water; Landscapes
  - A postcard of fuel vendors in Port Said (Port Said - Vendeur de Combustible)., Circa 1899-1908; ref569; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Group Portraits; Outdoors; Street Vendors; Port Said, Egypt; Men; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; French Writing; English Writing; Facial Hair
  - A postcard of a woman with child in Port Said (Port Said - femme avec enfant)., Circa 1899-1908; ref570; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Group Portraits; Women; Children; Regional/National Dress; Port Said, Egypt; Head Covers/Veils; French Writing; English Writing
  - A postcard of women and children in a village near Port Said (Port Said - Village Arabe)., Circa 1899-1908; ref571; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Port Said, Egypt; Postcards; Women; Children; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; French Writing; English Writing; Palm Trees; Buildings; Irrigation; Head Covers/Veils; Group Portraits; Water
  - A postcard of the statue of Ferdinand de Lesseps at Port Said (Port Said - Ferdinand de Lesseps)., Circa 1899-1908; ref572; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Port Said, Egypt; Lighthouses; Statues/Sculptures; Monuments/Memorials; Buildings; Boats/Ships; Men; Transportation; Seas; Mediterranean Sea; French Writing; English Writing
  - A postcard of a ship in the Suez Canal at Port Said (Port Said - Le Canal de Suez)., Circa 1899-1908; ref573; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Seas; Mediterranean Sea; Canals; Port Said, Egypt; Boats/Ships; Transportation; French Writing; English Writing; Buildings
  - A postcard of the statue of Ferdinand de Lesseps at Port Said (Port Said - Ferdinand de Lesseps)., Circa 1899-1908; ref574; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Seas; Mediterranean Sea; Buildings; Lighthouses; Men; Statues/Sculptures; Monuments/Memorials; French Writing; English Writing; Port Said, Egypt
  - A postcard of boats on the Nile in Cairo., Circa 1899-1908; ref575; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Cairo, Egypt; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Mediterranean Sea; English Writing
  - A hand-colored postcard of an illustration of a general view of Cairo (Series 635/8)., Circa 1899-1908; ref576; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Hand-colored Photographs/Hand-tinting; Cairo, Egypt; Buildings; Architecture; Pyramids; Religious Sites; Mosques; English Writing; French Writing; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Giza, Egypt
  - A hand-colored postcard of the Giza Pyramids., Circa 1899-1908; ref577; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Hand-colored Photographs/Hand-tinting; Pyramids; Architecture; Palm Trees; Nile River; Buildings; Animals; Men; Camels; English Writing; Giza, Egypt; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts
  - A postcard of a man walking with camels in front of the Funerary Complex of Emir Qurqumas (Tombs of the Khalifs)., Circa 1900-1950; ref578; Castro Brothers Editors - Cairo; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Funerary complexes of Emir Qurqumas and Sultan al-Ashraf Inal; Animals; Camels; Buildings; Architecture; Mosques; Religious Sites; Men; Regional/National Dress; Cairo, Egypt; English Writing; Tombs/Mausoleums
  - A postcard of a man praying and a camel in a desert outside Cairo., Circa 1900-1950; ref579; Castro Brothers Editors - Cairo; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Men; Praying; Animals; Camels; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Deserts; Cairo, Egypt; English Writing; Landscapes
  - A postcard of a man riding a camel departing from the Sahara., Circa 1900-1950; ref580; Castro Brothers Editors - Cairo; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Men; Animals; Camels; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Cairo, Egypt; Deserts; English Writing; Landscapes
  - A postcard of a man on a camel in front of the The Pyramids in Cairo (no. 165), Circa 1900-1950; ref581; Lehnert & Landrock; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Pyramids; Giza, Egypt; Animals; Camels; Men; Regional/National Dress; Architecture; Monuments/Memorials; Nile River; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts
  - A hand-colored postcard of an illustration of The Great Sphinx at Giza., Circa 1900-1950; ref582; Lehnert & Landrock; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Giza, Egypt; The Great Sphinx of Giza; Pyramids; Architecture; Monuments/Memorials; Buildings; Men; Animals; Regional/National Dress; English Writing; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Hand-colored Photographs/Hand-tinting
  - A postcard of men on camels in front of The Sphinx in Cairo., Circa 1900-1950; ref583; Vitta & C. ie, Le Caire - Port Said & Alexandrie; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; The Great Sphinx of Giza; Giza, Egypt; Pyramids; Monuments/Memorials; Architecture; Group Portraits; Outdoors; Men; Animals; Camels; Regional/National Dress; English Writing; French Writing; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts
  - A postcard of boats in the Mahmoudiyah (Mahmoudieh) Canal in Alexandria., 11 August 1918; ref584; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Alexandria, Egypt; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Canals; Men; English Writing
  - A postcard of a man and two camels in the Desert (no.128)., Circa 1900-1950; ref585; Lehnert & Landrock; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Egypt; Camels; Animals; Men; English Writing; Individual Portraits; Deserts; Regional/National Dress
  - A postcard of the excavated Sphinx., Circa 1900-1950; ref586; Lehnert & Landrock; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Giza, Egypt; Pyramids; The Great Sphinx of Giza; Architecture; Monuments/Memorials; English Writing; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts
  - A postcard of an illustration of a birds eye view of the Suez Canal (no. 324)., Circa 1900-1950; ref587; The Oriental and Commercial Bureau, Port Said, Egypt; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Egypt; Maps; Mediterranean Sea; Red Sea; Seas; French Writing; German Writing; English Writing; Landscapes
  - A hand-colored postcard of a street in Suez (Serie 652)., Circa 1899-1908; ref588; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Hand-colored Photographs/Hand-tinting; Men; Women; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Buildings; Architecture; Suez, Egypt; Streets/Roads; English Writing
  - A hand-colored postcard of the market street in Suez (Serie 652)., Circa 1899-1908; ref589; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Hand-colored Photographs/Hand-tinting; Men; Women; Streets/Roads; Buildings; Shops; Markets; Regional/National Dress; Suez, Egypt
  - A postcard of people sitting under an awning in a street in Port Said (Port Said - Rue Arabe, serie 205)., Circa 1900-1950; ref590; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Port Said, Egypt; Men; Streets/Roads; Architecture; English Writing; French Writing
  - A postcard of a street in Port Said (Port Said - Rue Arabe, serie 205)., Circa 1900-1950; ref591; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Port Said, Egypt; Buildings; Architecture; Men; French Writing; English Writing; Street Lamps; Carriages/Coaches; Animals; Horses; Streets/Roads; Group Portraits; Fez/Tarboush; Regional/National Dress; Transportation
  - A postcard of sugar cane vendors in Port Said (no. 109)., Circa 1922-1936; ref592; Lehnert & Landrock; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; English Writing; Street Vendors; Men; Women; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Buildings; Animals; Port Said, Egypt; Postal Stamps; Postal Stamps; Donkeys; Food; Group Portraits; Facial Hair
  - A postcard of Lesseps Avenue in Port Said (Avenue de Lesseps 412), Circa 1902-1912; ref593; Lichtenstern & Harari, Commission Agents, Cairo (Egypt) (Active circa 1901-1908); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Port Said, Egypt; English Writing; French Writing; Streets/Roads; Individual Portraits; Buildings; Architecture; Arabic Writing; Men
  - A hand-colored postcard of four children with baskets (Fellahine Ramassant le Fumier), Circa 1902-1912; ref594; Lichtenstern & Harari, Commission Agents, Cairo (Egypt) (Active circa 1901-1908); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Group Portraits; Children; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Seas; Buildings; French Writing; Outdoors; Girls; Hand-colored Photographs/Hand-tinting
  - J. J. Smith. R. A. S. C., Circa 1932; 1 Photographic Prints